Getting trapped in a movie... is no day at the beach.
Teen Beach Movie is a family, music, tv movie film directed by Jeffrey Hornaday.
Life's a beach for surfers Brady and McKenzie – until a rogue wave magically transports them inside the classic '60s beach
party flick, "Wet Side Story," where a full-blown rivalry between bikers and surfers threatens to erupt.
There, amidst a sea of surfing, singing and dancing, Brady and Mack accidentally change the
storyline, and the film’s dreamy hero and heroine fall for them instead of for each other!
Brady, played by Ross Lynch.
McKenzie 'Mack' Fox, played by Maia Mitchell.
Lela, played by Gracie Gillam.
Tanner, played by Garrett Clayton.
Butchy, played by John DeLuca.
Cheechee, played by Chrissie Fit.
Teen Beach Movie is a 2013 American musical teen romantic comedy
film released as a Disney Channel Original Movie.
Directed by Jeffrey Hornaday and written by Vince Marcello, Mark
Landry, Robert Horn, it was filmed in Puerto Rico.
The movie premiered on July 19, 2013, on Disney Channel
and stars Ross Lynch and Maia Mitchell.
Teen Beach Movie was the only Disney Channel Original Movie to premiere in 2013.
A sequel, Teen Beach 2, premiered on June 26, 2015.
The film explores themes of surfer, time travel,
musical, film in film, teen movie.
The tone is lighthearted.